(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T00:10:58.989380",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
風の吹く夜に
On a windy night,
チェンジしよう ざわめく色彩は
let's change, the rustling colors
あなたが走ることもきっとないんでしょう
you probably won't even run, will you?
推しの曲 めっちゃいいね
Your oshi's song is so good!
みるハコチャンス
Miruhako Chance!
みるハコなら 臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる
With Miruhako, enjoy immersive oshi content!
みるハコ最高
Miruhako is the best!
推し活も増やそう みるハコ
Expand your oshi activities with Miruhako!
みるハコ by JOYSOUND
Miruhako by JOYSOUND
推しの曲 めっちゃいいね
Your favorite song is so good!
みるハコチャンス！
Miruhako Chance!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりでおしのコンテンツが楽しめる！
With Miruhako, you can enjoy your favorite content with full realism!
みるハコ最高！ 音も増やそう！ みるハコ！
Miruhako is the best! Let's turn up the volume too! Miruhako!
あ、聞こえてますか？
Ah, can you hear me?
やった！みんな見えてるよー！
Yay! I can see all of you!
えー、緊張してます、はい。
Uh, I'm nervous, yep.
はい、ということで、もうそろそろ、遠乃夜宵初のソロライブ「BREAK YOURS」が始まるぞー！
Alright, so, Tono Yomi's first solo live "BREAK YOURS" is about to begin!
声がすごいじゃん！
Your voices are incredible!
一緒に盛り上がる準備はできて るかー！
Are you ready to get hyped together?!
声出す準備もできて るかー！行くぞー！
Are you ready to make some noise?! Let's go!
聞かせて？
Let me hear it?
みんな、今日はここまでと、ラスト揃いに行ってくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you so much for coming all the way here and gathering for the finale!
最後まで、盛り上がって行くぞー！
Let's get hyped right to the very end!
全身素敵なバイオレット
Covered in an elegant violet from head to toe
とんがって参上、悪魔って最強
An unexpected visit, the devil is the strongest
あなたの背中に闇をつけて
Cloaking your back with darkness
小悪魔だって恐ろしい
Even the little devils are scary
完全極楽墜を提唱
Persuading you to sink into the absolute paradise
抗って細胞、振り切って最強
The remaining cells trying to resist, to shake off the strongest
自堕落症状鎖付き
Chained with this syndrome of depravity
あくまで秘密の種も付き
Coming with the secret seed planted by the devil
何千回も爪を研いで機を窺って
Claws sharpened a thousand times, waiting for the chance to strike
洗脳完了これで誕生
Brainwashing completed, now the emotions will last eternally
永遠に尽くそうだろう
As an order from the underworld,
悪魔界指令は唄えて
yes, come sing with me
常闇じゃないなら渦を巻く
If the darkness is yet everlasting, we'll be swirling it up
デビデビ不思議解明
Devi devi, explaining the inconceivable
ビビビビ墜落の底から
Bibibibi, from the depths of corruptness
人間界ハードなんて
Why is it so difficult to survive in this world
常識がないなら奪われる
You'll be robbed if you don't have the wits
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
影を撃って
Shoot down the shadows
イェイ
Yay
完全無欠のバイオレット
This perfectly flawless violet
切り込んでハイに、取り込んで倍に
Marching in with high spirits, taking and duplicating
あなたの心に忍び込み
Sneakily creeping into your heart
小悪魔だって恐ろしい
Even the little devils are scary
刻む我、奇を衒う、ならば
Carved into me, showing off my queerness, if so
他に誰？敵は誰？メンション
Who else? Who are enemies? Bring it up
下界旅、つける錆、あれば
This trip in the overworld, the rust adding up, if exists
君等ナビ、期待してんぜ
You navigators, I am anticipating
悪魔界指令は繋いで
As an order from the underworld, yes, we'll unite
相手にならないと管を巻く
If you're too weak to be considered an enemy, just shut up
デビデビご都合証明
Devi devi, proving the benefits
ビビビビ世界はフィクション
Bibibibi, this world is merely fiction
健全なモードなんて
How is this a healthy mode?
今だけは全てを恨めない
Only now that the resentment towards everything stops
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
闇を知って
Knowing the darkness well
イェイ
Yay
消えない寂しさと癒えない傷をつけ
Immortality, the loneliness coming with it
歩みをやめないなんて、ほう
Leaving behind wounds that never heal
わかった人間は時代を制御占領して光を生み出した
The knowledged mankind, dominating and illuminating this era
悪魔のような所業ね、あぁ
Isn't that what the devil does, ah
謳った文明で
in this roaring civilization
悪魔界指令は唄えて
As an order from the underworld, yes, come sing with me
常闇じゃないなら渦を巻く
If the darkness is yet everlasting, we'll be swirling it up
デビデビ不思議解明
Devi devi, explaining the inconceivable
ビビビビ墜落の底から
Bibibibi, from the depths of corruptness
人間界ハードなんて
Why is it so difficult to survive in this world
常識がないなら奪われる
You'll be robbed from if you don't have the wits
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
影を撃って
Shoot down the shadows
悪魔界指令は繋いで
As the alliance of the underworld, yes, we'll unite
相手にならないと管を巻く
If you're too weak to be considered an enemy, just shut up
デビデビご都合証明
Devi devi, proving the benefits
ビビビビ世界はフィクション
Bibibibi, this world is merely fiction
健全なモードなんて
How is this a healthy mode?
今だけは全てを恨めない
Only now that the resentment towards everything stops
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
闇を知って
Knowing the darkness well
イェイ
Yay
どっちが！
Which one!
聞いたぞ！
I heard you!
やべ、めっちゃ緊張した
Man, I was so nervous.
え、みんなが目の前にいますよ！
Uh, everyone is right in front of me!
え、見えてる？みんな！
Uh, can you see me? Everyone!
やばい、緊張伝わった？
Oh no, did my nervousness get across?
やめて！
Stop it!
はい、ということで、こよぴー…
Right, so, Koyopī...
横浜の男ども、女子どもですー！
Men and women of Yokohama!
ちょっといっぱいお水のもう。口パッサパサなのよ。
Let me drink some water. My mouth is totally dry.
お水美味しい！キモすぎ！
Water is delicious! That's gross!
風じゃないよ、風じゃ。
It's not a cold, it's not!
ということで、皆さんえ、なんとソロライブ来ました！
So everyone, um, my solo live has arrived!
えー今日、みんなグッズ買ってくれた？
Um, did everyone buy goods today?
いや本当すごい！あのTシャツほら、もうなんかおそろコーデみたいになってる。
Man, this is amazing! Look at those T-shirts, they're like matching outfits.
いいね、すごい。で今ここでねしゃべりながらね緊張をほぐしてっていう…あ、もうすごい！緊張したよ！
That's great, amazing. And right now I'm talking while calming my nerves... Ah, man! I was so nervous!
まあまあまあまあ…まあいいんですよ、そんなのは。はい。
Well, well... It's fine, stuff like that. Yeah.
ということで、えー今日はね、えーライブのタオルとかもねこうちょっとこう持ちながらみんなでこう、イエーイとかってやっていきたいなとか思ってるのでね、えーぜひ首とかにかけて待っていてください。
So, while holding the live towels like this and going "Yay!", please keep them around your neck and wait.
はい、そしてね、なんとスタンディングということでみんな足大丈夫？
Right, and since it's standing, are everyone's legs okay?
もう元気そうだよね。
You look full of energy.
いいね、この笑い声が聞こえてくるのとかもすごい良い。いいよ、ありがとう。
It's great, hearing your laughter like this is so nice. That's good, thank you.
はい、でね、そのスタンディングなので周りにね気付けながらね、ぜひ最後まで一緒に盛り上げていけたらなと思います。
Right, and since it's standing, please be mindful of those around you and let's get hyped together until the very end.
そして、なんと今日はね現地の人だけじゃありません！インターネットから応援してくれてるみんなもいます！
And what's more, today isn't just for people here in person! Everyone cheering from the internet is here too!
イエーイ！
Yay!
はい、コメントも見えてますよ。ありがとうございます！
Yep, I can see the comments too. Thank you so much!
でね、なんとこの後もねたくさん歌う予定なんですけれども、あと2曲ほど歌ったら、えーYouTubeとツイッチのね今ねちょっとあのちらみせっていうのをやってるんですけどそちらが終わってしまいます。
And we're planning to sing a lot more after this, but after about two more songs, the preview on YouTube and Twitch will end.
共鳴するのやめてくれない？
Won't you stop resonating?
えー興味がある方はね、えーチケットをぜひ買っていただけたらなと思います。概要欄に書いてあるので、チェックチェックしてみてね！
For those interested, I hope you'll buy a ticket. It's in the description, so check it out!
1日中うるさいね！
You're noisy all day long.
ということでね、えーみんな準備はできてますか？準備もっとできてる人、大きい声もっと出してください。できてますか！
So anyway, is everyone ready? Those who are even more ready, give me a louder voice! Are you ready?!
はいということで、とこやみとわファーストソロライブ！ここから始まりだ！行くぞー！アクマ！
Right then, Tokoyami Towa's 1st Solo Live! It starts right here! Let's go! Akuma!
全身素適なバイオレット
Covered in an elegant violet from head to toe
とんがって参上、悪魔って最強
An unexpected visit, the devil is the strongest
あなたの背中に闇をつけ
Cloaking your back with darkness
小悪魔だって恐ろしい
Even the little devils are scary
完全極楽墜落を提唱
Persuading you to sink into absolute paradise
抗って細胞、振り切って最強
Resisting cells, shaking off the strongest
自墜落症状鎖付き、あくまで秘密の種も付き
Chained with the syndrome of depravity, with the devil's secret seed
何千回も爪を研いで機を窺い
Claws sharpened a thousand times, waiting for the chance
洗脳完了これで誕生
Brainwashing completed, now born
永遠に尽くそうだろう
Let's devote ourselves eternally
悪魔界指令はい歌って
As an order from the underworld, come sing
常闇がないなら渦を巻く
If the darkness is yet everlasting, we'll be swirling it up
デビデビ不思議解明
Devi devi, explaining the inconceivable
ビビビビ墜落の底から
Bibibibi, from the depths of corruptness
人間界ハードなんだって
Why is it so difficult to survive in this world
常識がないなら奪われる
You'll be robbed if you don't have the wits
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
影を撃ってイエイ
Shoot down the shadows, yay
完全無欠のバイオレット
This perfectly flawless violet
切り込んでハイに、取り込んで倍に
Cutting in high, taking in double
あなたの心に忍び込み
Sneakily creeping into your heart
小悪魔だって恐ろしい
Even the little devils are scary
刻む我、奇を衒う、ならば
Carved into me, showing off my queerness, if so
他に誰? 敵は誰? メンション
Who else? Who are enemies? Mention
下界旅、つける錆、あれば
This trip in the overworld, the rust adding up, if exists
全身素気ないバイオレット
Covered in an elegant violet from head to toe
とんがって参上、悪魔って最強
An unexpected visit, the devil is the strongest
(あなたの背中に闇をつけ
(Cloaking your back with darkness
小悪魔だって恐ろしい)
Even the little devils are scary)
完全極楽墜を提唱
Persuading you to sink into the absolute paradise
抗って細胞、振り切って最強
The remaining cells trying to resist, to shake off the strongest
(自堕落症状鎖付き
(Chained with this syndrome of depravity
あくまて秘密の種も付き)
Coming with the secret seed planted by the devil)
何千回も爪を研いで機を窺って
Claws sharpened a thousand times, waiting for the chance to strike
洗脳完了これで誕生永遠に尽くそうぜ
Brainwashing completed, now the emotions will last eternally
悪魔界伝令はいい歌って
As an order from the underworld, yes, come sing with me
常闇がないなら渦を巻く
If the darkness is yet everlasting, we'll be swirling it up
デビデビ不可思議解明
Devi devi, explaining the inconceivable
ビビビビ墜落の底から
Bibibibi, from the depths of corruptness
人間界ハードなんて
Why is it so difficult to survive in this world
常識がないなら奪われる
You'll be robbed if you don't have the wits
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
影を撃ってイエイ
Shoot down the shadows, yay
完全無欠のバイオレット
This perfectly flawless violet
切り込んでハイに、取り込んで倍に
Marching in with high spirits, taking and duplicating
(あなたの心に忍び込み
(Sneakily creeping into your heart
小悪魔だって恐ろしい)
Even the little devils are scary)
刻む我、奇を衒う、ならば
Carved into me, showing off my queerness, if so
他に誰？敵は誰？メンション
Who else? Who are enemies? Bring it up
下界旅、つける錆、あれば
This trip in the overworld, the rust adding up, if exists
君等ナナビ、期待してんぜ
You navigators, I am anticipating
悪魔界伝令はいい繋いで
As an order from the underworld, yes, we'll unite
相手にならないと管を巻く
If you're too weak to be considered an enemy, just shut up
デビデビご都合証明
Devi devi, proving the benefits
ビビビビ世界はフィクション
Bibibibi, this world is merely fiction
健全なモードなんて
How is this a healthy mode?
今だけは全てを恨めない
Only now that the resentment towards everything stops
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
闇を知ってイエイ
Knowing the darkness well, yay
消えない寂しさと癒えない傷をつけ
Immortality, the loneliness coming with it
歩みを止めないなんて、ほう
Leaving behind wounds that never heal
わかった人間は
"I'll never stop going forward"
時代を御し占領して光を生み出した
The knowledged mankind
悪魔のような所業ね、あぁ
Dominating and illuminating this era
謳った文明で
Isn't that what the devil does? Ah, in this roaring civilization
悪魔界伝令はいい歌って
As an order from the underworld, yes, come sing with me
常闇がないなら渦を巻く
If the darkness is yet everlasting, we'll be swirling it up
デビデビ不可思議解明
Devi devi, explaining the inconceivable
ビビビビ墜落の底から
Bibibibi, from the depths of corruptness
人間界ハードなんて
Why is it so difficult to survive in this world?
常識がないなら奪われる
You'll be robbed if you don't have the wits
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
影を撃って
Shoot down the shadows
悪魔界伝令はいい繋いで
As the alliance of the underworld, yes, we'll unite
相手にならないと管を巻く
If you're too weak to be considered an enemy, just shut up
デビデビご都合証明
Devi devi, proving the benefits
ビビビビ世界はフィクション
Bibibibi, this world is merely fiction
健全なモードなんて
How is this a healthy mode?
今だけは全てを恨めない
Only now that the resentment towards everything stops
デビデビ悪魔なの
Devi devi, this is the devil
闇を知って
Knowing the darkness well
まだまだもっと
Still, still more!
声出して行けるんじゃないの！
We can go even higher, right?!
だって私いつまでもずっと鳥籠気味
This has been me, forever and ever
外海はもうありえない
The outside world is already out of reach
ちょっと失望フラフラ
A bit of disappointment, flustered
そっぽ向くの思わせぶりユレスたないからさ
Making me turn my back on it all
好きだって嫌いだってこうなんて
Liked or hated, whatever!
目覚めしてもし無理だって、無理だってできるよって
If you wake up and cry, "No way," saying it's impossible
ガラスハートをクリアもして
Garish hearts, let's clear them away
骨の髄まで絞り尽くして
Stabbing through to the bone marrow, exhausting it all
壊れほどまどわせて
Pushing my sanity to the absolute breaking point
ユーモア、ユーモア、油断を
Don't hesitate, don't let your guard down!
ラビューとヒューラ転がして
Love you, too? Let's roll with it!
ドキキングを駆け巡って、痺れる声を
Let your piercing screams echo through the night
雷鳴へ
Raise it higher!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
The free part has ended!
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!